大家好
我是小舞
今天和大家一同观赏的是
2017年苏迪曼杯半决赛
第二盘男子单打的较量
由中国选手林丹对阵日本选手西本拳
太五比三
西本控转身单反拍过度控正手嗯
双方网前较量
单控网抢攻得分
He's getting used to the conditions
But it's also the first time
He placed in immotto
And and obviously
He has been
五平基本控
正手抢放网单接杀转对角网前扑球
西本顶后场摆脱单过度
后场双方右半区对拉
单连续平高控正手
西本平高空头顶单接杀转对角得分
六比五
单控正手抓过度进攻
基本高质量挡网得分
哎呀哈哈
Uh
And that deflected it
A little bit inwards
And and then the state in uji here
It's clearly going wide uh
but this touch呃
just8比七
单接杀高质量挡斜线得分
八平单直接抓推突击得分
九比十
单控正手放中路远网
西本回放单网前分对角得手
Just carested over
十比12
西本推头顶单软押宝
主动双方网前较量
西本抓推单接杀高质量挡斜线得分
Yeah
An amazing touch here from from lindan
Is quite low in in defense there
And and still he manages to uh
13比十
西本停顿推转身控网
单抓过度下压
双方往前较量
单控转身
西本平高拉开抓过度杀上网连贯得分
He should try to do more uh
However
Difficult it may be
But but this see here
He changes the speed attacks
And then follows up
and and13平单假动作分球基本控正手
但同样控正手
西本抓推推球逼过度
侧身杀斜线单
超强防守反击得手
Brilliant swinner as almost a trademark counter
Attack here from linden watch
How he's in control
Even though he's
He's on the floor
14平单连续控正手in making lindwork
More than than he did in the in the beginning of the of the game
西本同样控正手平高
空头顶单下压保
主动控正手单抓过度进攻
空头顶再度抓过度进攻
单控头顶抓摆脱头顶劈直线得分
That's in this
But it was he always felt that chinese man was in control
Yeah
Exactly
And and then very good
15比14
双方抽档较量
往前较量
西本假放真推得手
4.75平
单控正手
西本同样控正手抓过度下压单挡斜线
摆脱西本弹后场逼过度
单接杀挡斜线摆脱西本再度进攻
被单轻松化解
单控转身抓过度
头顶突击一拍基本弹
后场破坏连贯
西本劈杀上网
但往前推扑出界
就一个maybe啊
18比17基本抓推
双方网前较量
单推球逼过度
头顶杀一拍
抽压追身
西本回抽直线摆脱控网
但抓推失误
He knows that linden uh
It's likely to do this shot from here
Waits for it that
18平单控正手抓过度杀上网连贯得分
Trying to make a winner from uh from the smash
The first smash
then he19比18
基本控正手控网
单推球拉开放网
基本控正手单控头顶抓平高头顶点杀对角得分
Saved it for when he needed it has done a lot of straight
Attacking from the backend
20比18单抓推
西本控头顶单软压宝
主动控头顶往前蓝调一拍
平高拉开
西本连续控正手
西本抓过度进攻
单挡直线化解平高拉开西本过渡
后场单滑拍直线
西本连续控两底线
单软押宝主动控头顶
西本接调转对角
劈杀斜线得分
Oh that's brilliant played very well
In this rally
Both players
Managing to for a long time to to keep the opponent away from
19比20
双方互相控正手抽档较量
单抓推
西本同样抓推往前扑压被防
最终西本抓推失误单拿下了首局比赛的胜利
第二局一比零单控正手基本控
正手抓过度进攻得分
二比零单控正手西本过度直线抓推突击得手
Oh yes
From value through his footwork
And this one
Is
It's the forearm here
一比四
单控正手抓过度
劈掉斜线
高质量回搓得分
二比四
单控正手基本下压
单接杀转对角得分
Again good control in the front court
三比四单接杀挡斜线
摆脱抓推控网抢攻
单抓平高
头顶杀对角
双方互相控正手
单滑拍直线抓过度
高质量劈吊得分
Too much in control in in the first rallies of uh
the second game and4平基本控正手嗯
但同样控正手抓过度
侧身杀斜线得分
No and from winning fall off now
Uan issue
Motto is uh has lost five in a row
And and the trouble is is on his side of of the net
六比五单控正手抓过度下压
往前扑杀得分
That he's been a little bit more offensive
A bit
More aggressive in this second game
Exactly
六平西本控网单控正手
往前拦掉一拍
控正手西本抽压追身
单抓推
西本同样抓推
放远网
高质量P掉得分
Just the deflects the the tape of net here
And thus is is becoming shorter than
What you would expect
But yeah
And he just makes his extra stretch
and he's actually not8平七本抓推
但同样抓推
单抓过度进攻
往前分
对角西本控转身再控头顶抓摆脱进攻
单超强防守反击得分
Great point playing well
But again
I have this feeling that that
Physically
He's uh
He has his limits and baby star
九比八西本抓推
双方网前较量
西本进攻单弹
后场破坏连贯
网前停顿
西本空头顶单下压西本弹
后场逼摆脱头顶进攻得分
11比九单假动作分球基本回放
重杀中路追身单防反
西本接杀
转对角单放网进攻连贯得分
12比十
双方网前较量
单抓推突击得分
11比十
二基本控正手控网
但同样控正手嗯
停顿推正手底线得分
12平
单控正手基本下压钓鱼
但抓扑失误哎
See this one
And the issumoto is already rushing to the back
And and the timing is totally often
13比14单控正手抓过度进攻
往前扑压
被防单蓝调假杀真吊得分
Great deception
Yeah
And of course
He also knows that linden has a little bit of uh
Ubad feeling about the cross court smash uh
But lindan knows that he has to he has to attack in both sides
And and then he chooses to do this
16比14单控正手抓过度
头顶突击一拍
双方往前较量
西本下压单抓推西本弹后场破坏连贯
抓过度进攻
单挡网化解基本停顿
放网单控头顶抓过度
头顶突击直线得分
It's wonderful moment of recovery
There's one again
He's up straight away
Yeah
He's very low
17比14
西本分球抢攻
单丝滑卸力挡网杀
上网连贯得分
Let's see to think eighty four days
Yeah
He knows that can can he make these changes
18比14
基本控正手单抽直线摆脱西本控正手抓过度
侧身突击得分清
16比20
西本平高空头顶抓过度进攻
单控正手基本下压空头顶
单抓推高点分球
西本连续控正手
双方互相控正手
单抓过度
头顶突击
直线假杀真吊终结比赛
在第一排混双失利的情况下
力挽狂澜
以20一比19
第16战胜日本选手基本全开
为中国队在这场半决赛中扳回一城
And china on the board in the main singles
Courtesy of lyndan is great great champion
It's the final point and whereas a younger player
Would would proudly
Have tried to finish it for uh
All the match point earlier than lindjust shows uh
A lot of experience
And a lot of patients until he
He said something
Himself for these two very skilled from drop shots
One in either side
But all credit to ukti motor
He uh he bought